One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Law...
Law...
Go...
Git...
2nd Basement Floor
İkinci Bodrum Katı
My real name is...
Benim asıl ismim...
Trafalgar D. Water Law.
Trafalgar D. Water Law.
Is that a secret?
İsmini mi sakladın?
Yes.
Evet.
I'm surprised. So you have a D. in your name, too.
Şaşırdım. Senin isminde de "D." var.
I'm telling you because I trust you.
Güvendiğimden söyledim sana.
Thank you.
Teşekkür ederim.
But... I don't have any answers for you.
Fakat ben de bilmiyorum.
Luffy might not care,
Luffy pek önemsemese de...
but personally...
ben...
I want to learn the meaning of D., too.
D'nin manasını çok merak ediyorum.
So all we can do is follow the red stones?
Kırmızı olanlar şart anlaşılan.
Indeed...
Öyle duruyor.
And that means toppling the Four Emperors.
Yonkolar'ı yenmemiz gerek yani.
It's not as if they'll just hand them over, after all.
Bize öylece vereceklerini zannetmiyorum çünkü.
This isn't it...
Bu olmaz.
It needs to be red.
Kırmızılardan lazım.
In some places, the people of the D. have been called...
Bir yerlerde D'li kişiler çağrılıyor.
"the Natural Enemies of the Gods!"
"Tanrıların Ezeli Düşmanları!"
Hey, Cora...
Hey, Cora-san...
I still wanna know...
kusura bakma...
why I have to lead...
ama bu inişli çıkışlı kaderin manasını...
such a checkered life.
öğrenmek istiyorum.
Usopp! Are you okay?!
Usopp, iyi misin?
Who d'ya think I am?!
Kim siniyursun beni?
I'm most certainly not okay...
Masil iyi oliyim?
No, you most certainly aren't...
İyi durumda olamazsın tabii.
But at the very least, I am.
Neyse ki ben iyi durumdayım.
Seriously?
Hey!
Flame Clouds
Alev Bulutları
Hey, Otama. How did you get here?
Hey, Otama. Buraya nasıl geldin?
One of the enemies gave me a boat ride!
Düşman gemisine bindik.
What?! An enemy?!
Ne?! Düşmanın mı?
Pay-Pay! Chew that dog up!
Pay-Pay! Şu köpeği parça pinçik et!
Do it yourself!
Sen yapsana.
Damn! What's with this baboon?!
Tüküreyim! Ne iş bu babun?
Wherever did he come from?!
Bu nereden çıktı ya?
Hihimaru!
Hihimaru!
Keep them busy for three minutes!
Onları 3 dakika oyala.
Those two mean business! That giant monkey will get hurt!
Onlar çok tehlikelidir. O dev maymuna zarar verirler.
Don't underestimate us, Onami!
Bizi küçük görme, Onami-chan!
We came here...
Buraya...
as samurai!
samuray olarak geldik!
Get out of my way!
Açın yolu!
We can do this forever, Young Master Yamato.
Bu işin sonu yok, Genç Efendi Yamato.
Although, I can't go losing any more of my impregnable Armored Division.
Böyle desem de zırhlı birliğimi kaybetmek istemem.
How dare you harm so many of them?!
Tonla adamımı haşat ettiniz.
Aim!
Nişan al!
Fire!
Ateş!
Momonosuke! Shinobu!
Momonosuke-kun! Shinobu-san!
Yamato...
Yamato...
If you keep taking bullets...
Bu kadar mermi yersen...
This is nothing.
Bir şey olmaz.
If you are a samurai, then you must decide!
Eğer samuraysan yapılması gerekeni yap!
Leave me here and take Lord Momonosuke...
Beni arkada bırakıp efendimi buradan...
No!
Olmaz!
If it were Oden...
Oden...
If it were Kozuki Oden...
Kozuki Oden...
he would never do that!
böyle bir şey yapmazdı!
How stubborn...
Ne kadar inatçı...
Do you really think you can defeat me while you're fretting over those weaklings?
Feci güçlü olsanız da o iki eziği korurken beni alt edebileceğinizi sanıyorsanız...
What arrogance, Young Master Yamato!
hayal görüyorsunuz derim, Genç Efendi Yamato.
Sasaki...
Sasaki...
What just happened?!
N'oldu?
Outta my way! Outta my way!
Çekilin, çekilin!
Get outta my way!
Çekilin yoldan!
Franosuke!
Franosuke!
Huh? Momo?!
Ha? Momo?!
Good to see you alive and kicking! Shinobu, you doing okay there?!
Hayattasın, ne güzel. Shinobu, sen de iyi durumdasın di' mi?
That's...
Bu...
I know him! He's part of Luffy's crew!
Tanıyorum seni! Luffy'nin tayfasından...
Cyborg Franky! He's worth 94 million berries!
Sayborg Franky! Kelle Ödülü 94 milyon beli.
It's hard to believe he's real!
Gerçekmiş!
Haccha?! Why are you here?!
Haccha?! Ne arıyorsun burada?
Oh no, not good!
Durum sakat!
Don't you dare, dumbass!
Yapma, aptal!
Is this because you couldn't catch me?! How childish!
Yakalayamadın diye sinirlendin mi? Çocuk musun sen?
Armored Division! Don't lose them! Keep them from running at any cost!
Zırhlı Birlik, onları gözden kaybetmeyin! Kaçmalarına izin vermeyin!
He broke the floor!
Yer çöktü.
Oh, right! There's a floor beneath us!
Aşağıya gidebiliriz sahi!
Momonosuke! Shinobu! Let's make our way down like this!
Momonosuke-kun! Shinobu-san! Bu yolla aşağıya kaçalım!
Momo! Shinobu! Are you okay?!
Momo! Shinobu! İyi misiniz?
Did you get caught?!
Sizi yakaladı mı?
No! This is an ally!
Hayır, bize yardım ediyor.
Cyborg Franky! I'll leave the enemy to you!
Sayborg Franky, burasını halledersin.
Who are you?!
Sen kimsin?
Luffy entrusted these two to me!
Luffy, bu ikisini bana emanet etti.
I don't know who you are...
Kimsin bilmiyorum ama...
but I got it! You can super count on me!
tamam! Süper güvenebilirsin bana!
Shinobu, take Momonosuke!
Shinobu-san, Momonosuke-kun'u tut!
What?
Ne?
I wanna return a favor!
İyilik borcumu ödeyeyim.
I'll be right back!
Hemen geliyorum.
I gotta take him down at least...
Bari şu herifi indireyim!
Narikabura Arrow!
Çınlayan Ok!
Narikabura
Çınlayan
Arrow
Arrow
Alright!
Halloldu.
That stranger did this?!
O mu yaptı bunu?
Who was that?
Kim ki o?
Haccha?!
Haccha?!
Dammit!
Siktir!
Yamato took Momonosuke down that hole!
Yamato, Momonosuke'yi alıp aşağıya kaçtı!
Organize a pursuit unit! Chase after them now!
Takip ekibi kurun! Derhal peşlerine düşün!
Armored Division! Let's deal with the damn robot!
Zırhlı Birlik, biz şu hurda yığınını parçalayacağız.
Momonosuke!
Momonosuke-kun!
You must survive!
Sen hayatta kalmalısın!
Survive at any cost!
Mutlaka hayatta kalmalısın.
The one who'll lead the world to a new dawn...
Dünyayı yeni şafağa taşıyacak olan...
is you!
sensin!
Kaido!
Kaido!
How annoying!
Canımı sıkıyorsun!
You've already lost, you fools!
Kaderiniz çoktan mühürlendi, sizi zavallılar!
She's coming!
Geliyor!
Big Mom is back!
Big Mom geri döndü!
Don't worry! I'm only interested in going...
Endişelenmeyin. Tek derdim,
up to where Kaido is.
Kaido'nun olduğu yere çıkmak.
I know how to fight the virus!
Virüsle mücadele etme yolunu buldum!
You do?!
Sahiden mi?
Run, Apoo!
Kaç, Apoo!
You'd better not let this show end just yet!
Gösteri hemen bitmesin!
Omasa!
Omasa!
Hey! Come to your senses!
Hey! Kendine gel!
There's no other option, huh?
O aşamaya geldik mi?
No... I've finally made it this far...
Hayır! Buraya kadar gelmiştim!
I don't want to die here!
Burada ölmek istemiyorum!
Please, help me...
Yardım et!
He's still on my tail!
Hâlâ peşimde.
What a pain! He won't give it a rest!
Yok böyle bir inat!
Apoo!
Apoo!
Give me the antibody!
Antikoru ver.
Drake, you bastard!
Drake piçi!
You're here! Back me up!
Geldin mi? Yardım et!
What are you doing?! We gotta fight him together!
N'apıyorsun? Onunla birlikte dövüşmemiz gerek.
Damn you!
Siktir!
Like I said, it isn't fair to fight me as a duet!
İkiye bir hiç adil değil işte!
He wants a solo against me!
Benimle teke tek kapışmak istiyor.
Isn't that right?!
Yanılıyor muyum?
Beats me what's going on here. I didn't expect you to be so chill with it!
Bu anlayışlılık nereden çıktı bilmiyorum ama var gücünle saldır bakalım!
Alright, then... Check it out!
Pekâlâ, öyleyse... Kulak ver!
What?!
Ne?!
Hey! Zoro!
Hey! Zoro!
Oh, Chopper.
Oo, Chopper.
Thanks!
Sağ ol.
Can I leave this floor to you?
Bu katı sana bıraksam ya?
I can't stay for the show.
Oyun oynayacak vaktim yok.
You'll live, right?
Ölmezsin di' mi?
Of course!
Elbette.
I've already figured out how the virus works!
Virüsün nasıl işlediğini çözdüm.
That's my guy!
Helal sana.
Third Floor
3. Kat
Is he gonna gather all the metal in the castle?!
Kaledeki tüm metali toplayacak mısın...
Dammit!
Kahretsin!
Eustass Captain Kid!
...Eustass "Kaptan" Kid?
Stop him! Don't let him get to the rooftop!
Durdurun şunu! Çatıya çıkmasın!
They're coming.
Geliyorlar.
Let me greet them...
Bu kodum mu oturtan yığınla karşılarım ben de!
It's fine if you don't move outta the way. Just come right to us!
Bizimle gelmek isteyen yoldan çekilmesin.
Do you think this is enough, Killer?!
Yeterli olur mu sence Killer?
Our enemy is the world's strongest pirate...
Düşmanımız dünyanın en güçlü korsanı.
You can never have too much.
Ne kadar çok, o kadar iyi.
You said it!
Aynen!
Stop Straw Hat!
Hasır Şapka'yı durdurun!
What floor are we on?!
Kaçıncı kattayız?
We're coming up on the third floor!
Bu kattan sonra üçüncü kat var.
The rooftop is above the fifth floor!
Çatı da beşinci katın üstünde.
Alright! Kin'emon, wait for me!
Pekâlâ! Kin'emon, bekle beni!
That's...
Bu...
Hey! Do you guys hear that?
Hey! Duydunuz mu?
Huh? Hear what?
Ha? Neyi?
Oh no... It's coming from the third floor!
Olamaz... Üçüncü kattan bir ses geliyor.
Whaddya say? Whaddya say?
Naz yapma kız!
Please don't!
N'olur yapmayın!
I need it!
Dayanamıyorum artık!
You ought not!
Yapmamalısınız!
How naughty!
Çok ayıp!
Wait for us, Kin'emon!
Bekle bizi, Kin'emon!
Which way is the rooftop?!
Çatı katı ne tarafta?
That way!
Bu tarafta!
Alright!
Pekâlâ!
Whaddya say? Whaddya say?
Naz yapma kız!
You ought not! You ought not!
Yapmamalısınız! Yapmamalısınız!
How naughty!
Çok ayıp!
I have something serious to attend to.
Önemli bir işim çıktı.
You guys, go ahead!
Siz önden gidin.
I'll catch up as soon as I'm done!
İşim biter bitmez size yetişirim!
I hear it!
Duyuyorum!
How naughty!
Çok ayıp!
A beautiful woman...
Güzel bir kadın...
is calling for help!
yardım çağırıyor!
How naughty!
Çok ayıp!
That's it, come here!
Gel şöyle yanacıma!
Oh, you ought not do this!
N'olur yapmayın!
You're a real cutie, so whaddya say?
Aşk kuşum, gel hele şöyle.
You ought not!
Yapmayın!
Whaddya say?
Gel kız!
Please stop!
Lütfen durun artık!
How naughty!
Çok ayıp!
Samurai-style sexual harassment!
Samuray ülkesinin cinsel taciz replikleri.
"Whaddya say?", "How naughty!"
Gel kız ve çok ayıp.
How naughty!
Çok ayıp!
Someone in a position of power is untying a helpless woman's kimono.
Nüfuz sahibi biri, çaresiz bir kadının kimonusunu çözüyor.
What the spinning woman loses with each turn...
Dönen kadının her dönüşte yalnızca elbisesi elden gitmiyor...
It's her dignity!
iffeti de gidiyor!
Just hold on! Help is on the way!
Yettim! Yardımına geldim!
Whaddya...?
Gel...
It's not right!
Gelmeyecek!
Stop it!
Yapma!
What?! What's this?!
Ne?! Bu ne?
How naughty!
Çok ayıp!
A spider web?!
Örümcek ağı mı?
Hey, stop that!
Hey, kesin şunu!
How naughty!
Çok ayıp!
– Naughty Trap!
– Edepsiz Tuzak!
Another perv in shining armor came...
Ahlak bekçisi bir sapık daha geldi.
Damn... It was a trap...
Tüküreyim. Tuzak mıymış?
Black Leg Sanji of the Straw Hat Pirates.
Hasır Şapkalar'dan Kara Bacak Sanji.
He's worth 330 million berries!
Kelle ödülü 330 milyon beli.
Probably competing with his crewmate Zoro.
Arkadaşı Zoro'yla yarışıyordu.
I think this one's bounty is higher.
Bunun ödülü daha yüksekti galiba.
Wow! We caught some big game!
Harika! Turnayı gözünden vurmuşuz.
Untie me now and I'll let this slide!
Hemen çözün beni! Affederim sizi.
Oh, how scary! You're blackmailing us!
Ay çok korkutucu. Bize şantaj yapıyor.
I have somewhere to be!
Gitmem gereken bir yer var!
If you go, the battlefield will just spill over.
Senin gitmenle savaş daha da büyür.
And I don't want this banquet hall to be caught up in it.
Bu ziyafet salonu da nasibini almasın, sağ ol.
My allies are waiting for me! Untie the damn rope already!
Dostlarım beni bekliyor! Çözün artık şu ipleri!
Boys with dirty mouths get me all tingly.
Arsız bir çocuksun bakıyorum da. İçim gıcıklandı.
"Boy"?! Stop messing with me!
Çocuk mu? Dalga geçme benimle!
Hey... what do you say?
Bak ne diyeceğim.
Do you...
Beni...
like me?
seviyor musun?
Cut it out! I don't...
Saçmalama! Ben...
I don't like you...
seni...
I love you!
seviyorum!
Elsewhere, on the Third Floor...
3. Katın Başka Bir Yerinde
Hey, Gorishiro! You're getting banana on me!
Hey, Gorishiro! Muz atıp durma artık!
Mizerka Beast Pirates Headliner Gorilla Smile Fruit
Mizerka Canavar Korsanları Öncüsü Goril Gülücük Meyvesi
Master Poker! Straw Hat and Jinbe are heading your way!
Poker-sama, Hasır Şapka ve Jinbe o tarafa doğru geliyor.
Yeah, got it.
Evet, güzel.
Poker Beast Pirates Headliner Rattlesnake Smile Fruit
Poker Canavar Korsanları Öncüsü Çıngıraklı Yılan Gülücük Meyvesi
Regrettably, I let Kid through...
Maalesef Kid'e engel olamadım...
But look! Straw Hat's bounty is 1.5 billion berries!
Ama bak, Hasır Şapka'nın ödülü 1,5 milyar beli.
Taking him down will do more than just clear my name!
Bunu haklarsam hatamı telafi eder, üstüne ödül bile alırım.
Aw, man! Come on!
Yeter artık ya!
Me, in the Soaring Six? That'll do nicely.
Tobi Roppo'ya girmek... Fena olmaz ha.
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
Hasır Şapka-san! Hasır Şapka-san!
This way!
Buradan!
Who are they?
Kim bunlar?
Oh, it's you guys!
Oo, siz miydiniz?
The ones from Udon!
Udon'daki adamlar!
Hey, Straw Hat isn't here yet?!
Hey, Hasır Şapka daha gelmedi mi?
He should be there soon!
Yakında orada olur.
A ladder...
El merdiveni...
Yeah, you can climb to the fourth floor with this.
Evet, bununla 4. kata geçebilirsiniz.
A bunch of enemies are waiting at the stairs.
Basamaklı merdivenlerde düşman pusmuş.
That helps a lot. Thanks!
Çok yardımı dokunur. Sağ olun.
Where is he?!
Gelmeyecek mi?
Everyone, listen up!
Beni dinleyin!
Use fire against the ice ogres!
Buz şeytanına karşı ateş kullanın!
This virus fuses with the gas that's chilling our bodies!
Bu virüs, vücutlarımızı donduran gazla birleştirilmiş!
Look at me!
Bana bakın!
If you stop the chill, the virus can't multiply!
Donmanızı engellerseniz virüs çoğalmaz!
Meanwhile, I'll make enough antibodies for everyone!
Herkese yetecek antikor üreteceğim!
I'm a doctor! I'll save everyone, both allies and enemies!
Ben doktorum! Dost düşman demeden herkesi kurtaracağım!
– What?!
– Ne?!
Everyone?! Including Omasa?!
Herkesi mi? Omasa'yı da mı?
So stay alive! Don't let that horrible man kill you!
Hayatta kalmaya bakın! O aşağılık adam yüzünden canınızdan olmayın!
How nice, tanuki!
Ağzın iyi laf yapıyor, tanuki.
And you're pathetic, Apoo!
Bir de sana bakalım, Apoo!
I presented you with such a fun little ogre game...
Mis gibi oyundu anasını satayım.
and you just had to go and ruin it!
Oyunumun içine edersiniz ha!
You two have gotten on my last nerve!
Siz ikiniz sinirimi bozuyorsunuz!
What?!
Ne?!
Screw the game!
Başlatma oyununa!
What?
Ne?
I didn't come to this island to play around with you losers!
Böyle sıkıcı bir oyunu oynamaya gelmedim bu adaya!
I came to chop up Kaido...
Dünyanın en güçlüsü denilen Kaido'yu...
the so-called strongest man in the world!
devirmeye geldim!
What?!
Ne?!
His anger triggered an earthquake?!
Öfkesi deprem mi yarattı?!
Was that conqueror's haki?!
Haki mi? Kralın hakisi mi?
Hold on to something! Everyone, hang in there!
Tutunun bir yerlere, dayanın millet!
Zoro, what did you do?! I can't believe you did this!
Zoro-san, ne yaptın öyle? Korkulası birisin!
There's no way that was me.
Benimle ne alakası var bunun?
What's with this shaking?!
Bu sarsıntı da ne?
I'm scared!
Korkuyorum.
No, I'm not scared!
Hayır, korkmuyorum!
You'll be fine! Just keep moving forward!
Bir şey olmayacak sana. Daha hızlı gidelim!
Let's hurry up!
Daha hızlı!
What's this?! Is it an earthquake, Jinbe?!
Bu ne?! Deprem mi Jinbe?
Geologically speaking, this island is unique, but...
Bu ada jeolojik olarak çok ender bir bölgede.
It's no use! We can't reach the shore!
Olacak gibi değil! Kıyıya gidemiyoruz!
Let's pull away from Onigashima for now!
Onigashima'dan şimdilik uzaklaşın!
What the...
Ne...
How impatient...
Sabırsızlığı üstünde.
Is the island sinking?!
Ada batıyor mu yoksa?
Onigashima's... What the hell is going on?!
Onigashima'ya... ne oluyor be?
Do you think the captain is okay?!
Kaptana bir şey olmaz umarım.
Port Area, Outside the Dome
Kubbenin Dışındaki Liman Bölgesi
Momonosuke! Your survival is the highest priority!
Momonosuke-kun, senin hayatta kalman birinci önceliğimiz.
Let's board a ship and get out of here!
Gemiye binip adadan ayrılalım!
We've gotta hurry.
Acele etmemiz gerek.
I have a bad feeling about this!
İçimde kötü bir his var!
What was that?
Bu neydi şimdi?
It stopped shaking.
Sarsıntı durdu.
I know how you feel, Zoro... I saw it, too.
Biliyorum Zoro, ben de gördüm.
Okiku's arm!
Okiku-chan'ın kolu!
Me as well!
Ben de gördüm.
I'm late to the party.
Başını kaçırdım.
I wish I could just fly there.
Oraya uçabilsem keşke.
But every route has its challenges.
Her yol ayrı bir savaş ama.
Straw Hats!
Hasır Şapkalar!
Marco the Phoenix!
Anka Kuşu Marco!
Yep, the one and only!
Ta kendisi.
You guys are the VIPs! Why are you still slumming it down here?
Ana birlik değil misiniz siz? Hâlâ bu katta ne oyalanıyorsunuz?
It's not like we want to be.
Biz de keyfimizden burada durmuyoruz.
Is there anything I can do to help?
Yapabileceğim bir şey var mı?
The Beast Pirates' ships... They're gone!
Canavar Korsanları'nın gemisi ortada yok.
What?!
Ne?!
So is the sea!
Deniz de yok!
What?! What do you mean by that?!
Ne?! Ne demek istiyorsun?
It's too late!
Geç kaldık.
We can no longer flee to the sea!
Denize kaçamayız artık!
Is this not a port?!
Burası liman değil mi?
That quake before...
Deminki sarsıntı...
I get it now!
Şimdi anladım.
What is going on, Yamato?!
Ne oluyor desene Yamato?!
Dragons fly through the air by creating flame clouds!
Ejderhalar oluşturdukları alev bulutlarıyla havada uçar.
That means that right now...
Yani şu an...
Kaido is making Onigashima fly!
Kaido, Onigashima'yı uçuruyor!
He's gonna relocate the island to the Flower Capital!
Adayı Çiçek Başkenti'ne indirecek!
N-No way...
Y-Yok artık.
Are you satisfied now?
Tatmin oldunuz mu?
The Kozuki are finished.
Kozuki'nin işi bitti.
Wano, or more accurately, New Onigashima,
Wano, daha doğrusu Yeni Onigashima,
will become a stronghold for pirates.
korsanların kalesi olacak.
Let's usher in a world of violence!
Kargaşa dolu dünyayı başlatalım!